Guide to the International Woodworkers of America Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Woodworkers of America records
1936-1987
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
4000
International Woodworkers of America
11.54 cubic feet (12 boxes)
Minutes, motions, convention proceedings and financial records of the union
Already source of labor unrest for several decades, the Pacific Northwest lumber and sawmill industry of the 1930s was in the midst of inter-union rivalry. The industry was dominated by single men working in remote and often inhospitable conditions. Support for communism was particularly strong in mill towns and logging camps populated with unskilled immigrant labor. Many of these Pacific Northwest woodworkers gathered in Portland in 1936 and formed the Federation of Woodworkers. Two years later, they opted to affiliate with the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) and became the International Woodworkers of America (IWA). Harold Pritchett was elected their first president. Pritchett had very strong ties to the Communist Party, although he consistently denied that he was a member. This affiliation, shared by many members of the IWA was a source of contention with the American Federation of Labor (AFL) and the US government. At first, this manifested as a struggle for IWA representation of woodworkers in the region. The AFL’s timber union, which eventually became the Lumber and Sawmill Workers (LSW), competed furiously for members. As a result IWA membership fell from about 40,000 at its first convention in 1937 to about 20,000 at its second in 1938. These early years were difficult for the IWA and marred by a disputes with the AFL timber union. Pritchett was directly affected when he was denied a permanent visa to the United States in 1940, which forced him to step down as leader of the union as he could not conduct business without access to both countries. However, he continued to work in Canada, quickly becoming president of District #1.
Turmoil persisted for much of the IWA's first two decades. Yet in spite of this the IWA grew rapidly. Wartime labor policies helped greatly. The Taft-Hartley Act (1948) caused the Canadian districts to attempt to disaffiliate, however this was defeated and they remained a part of the IWA until 1987. After the period of late 1940s anti-labor legislation, the IWA experienced great success. Several regionals convened for the first time in convention during the late 1950s and early 1960s. Union membership reached its peak in 1977 with 112,000. The 1980s were comparably difficult with industry-wide losses in union bargaining power. The IWA dissolved into two national unions in 1987.
A list of IWA Conventions with officers and nominations from 1936 to 1973 (with the exception of 1954, 1956, 1959-1962, 1964, 1970, 1972) can be found in folder 1/3.
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 4000-001, International Woodworkers of America records, 1936-1987
Accession No. 4000-002, International Woodworkers of America records, 1936-1942
Consult the scope and content information for each of the accessions listed below.
Open to all users.
Some records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
Kilgren, Thomas. “Harold Pritchett: Communism & the International Woodworkers of America.” last updated May 7, 2008. Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project. http://wayback.archive-it.org/3988/20140613002430/http://depts.washington.edu/civilr/Harold_Pritchett.html.
Lembcke, Jerry. Encyclopedia of the American Left, 2nd ed., s.v. “International Woodworkers of America.” New York, Oxford University Press, 1998.
Widenor, Marcus. Encyclopedia of U.S. Labor and Working-Class History, s.v. “International Woodworkers of America.” New York, Routledge, 2007.
See also International Woodworkers of America, Local 3-101 Records, Acc. Nos. 3120-001 and 3120-002 in Special Collections.
International Woodworkers of America$vArchives; Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union. Local 2532 (Portland, Ore.); Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Logging
- International Woodworkers of America records, 1936-1987; 4000-001; 11.4 cubic feet (10 boxes)
  This accession is organized into five series. SERIES I: HISTORICAL FEATURES, SERIES II: MINUTES, SERIES III: FINANCIAL RECORDS, SERIES IV: EXECUTIVE BOARD MOTIONS, and SERIES V: CONVENTION PROCEEDINGS. There are many financial records the vast majority of which are worked into the supplemental material in SERIES II: MINUTES. This collection documents the activities of IWA's leadership. It also documents the activities of the leadership of several of its regional councils within the SERIES II: MINUTES and SERIES V: CONVENTION PROCEEDINGS. The records from each council is arranged into their own subseries. Included amongst these councils are
  Western Canadian Regional #1 (Minutes and Convention Proceedings)
  Eastern Canadian Regional #2 (Convention Proceedings only)
  Western States Regional #3 (Minutes and Convention Proceedings)
  Midwestern States Regional #4 (Minutes and Convention Proceedings)
  Southern States Regional #5 (Minutes and Convention Proceedings)
  Klamath Basic District #6 (Convention Proceedings only)
  Plywood Box Shook, and Door Council #9 (Convention Proceedings only)
  Inland Empire District #10 (Convention Proceedings only)
  Most of the collected minutes for a set of meetings contain a transcript of the meeting and an associated supplemental document. For Subseries A: Executive Board in boxes 2-5 these supplemental sections were separated from the meeting's transcript placed in their own folders. These supplementals contain a variety of different documents referred to during the meetings. These include resolutions, correspondence, reports, financial information and reports, collected information and lists regarding IWA Locals, articles, legal documents, and other.
  Open to all users.
  Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
  U. of Oregon, March 02, 1989
  - Legacy Container List (Box-folder 1/1)
  - HISTORICAL FEATURES, circa 1975; SERIES I (Box-folder ½-3)
    - "History of the International Woodworkers of America.", circa 1975 (Box-folder ½)
    - "A History of the IWA Conventions and International Officers.", 1975 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - MINUTES, 1939-1985; SERIES II (Box-folder 1-6)
    - Executive Board, 1939-1983; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/4-5/25)
      - Executive Board includes bound copy, October 16, 17-20, 23 1939 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Executive Board, January-October 1940 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Executive Board, December 3-5 1940 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Executive Board bound copy, December 3-5 1940 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Executive Board bound copies, January-October 1940 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Executive Board includes bound copy, July 7 1941 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Executive Board, 1942 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Executive Board bound copies, 1942 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Executive Board, 1943 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Executive Board bound copies, 1943 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Executive Board, October 11 1960 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Executive Board, October 12 1960 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Executive Board, October 13 1960 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Executive Board, March 27-30 1961 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Executive Board (1 of 2), September 26-30,-October 6 1961 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Executive Board (2 of 2), September 26-30,-October 6 1961 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Executive Board, December 18 1961 (Box-folder ½0)
      - Executive Board, May 23-25 1962 (Box-folder ½1)
      - Executive Board, March 27-28 1963 (Box-folder ½2)
      - Executive Board, September 10-13, 20 1963 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1963 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Executive Board, December 4 1963 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1963 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Executive Board, May 13-14 1964 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1964 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Executive Board, September 28-29, October 5 1965 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Executive Board-Supplemental, 1965 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Executive Board, March 23-24 1966 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Executive Board, December 6 1966-December 8 1966 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1966 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Executive Board, May 3 1967-May 4 1967 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Executive Board, September 5-7 1967 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, September 5-7 1967 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Executive Board, March 27-28 1968 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Executive Board, September 18-19 1968 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1968 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Executive Board, November 12 1968 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Executive Board, May 26-27 1970 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Executive Board, October 28-29 1970 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, October 28-29 1970 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Executive Board, April 27-28 1971 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Executive Board, September 15-17, 24 1971 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1971 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Executive Board, December 14-15 1971 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1971 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Executive Board, April 12-13 1972 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Executive Board, October 18-20 1972 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1972 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Executive Board (1 of 2), April 4-6 1973 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Executive Board (2 of 2), April 4-6 1973 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental (1 of 2), 1963-1964, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental (2 of 2), 1963-1964, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Executive Board, September 19-21, 24 1973 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1973 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Executive Board, April 3-5 1974 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Executive Board, October 30-31 1974 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1974 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Executive Board, February 21 1975 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Executive Board, May 7-8 1975 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Executive Board, September 24-25 1975 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Executive Board, May 26 1976 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Executive Board, October 20-22 1976 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1976 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Executive Board, February 25-27, March 5 1976 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Executive Board, April 27-29 1977 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Executive Board, October 19-21, 28 1977 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1977 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Executive Board, November 1-2 1978 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1978 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Executive Board, April 25-27 1979 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Executive Board, February 3 1970 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Executive Board, July 23 1975 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Executive Board, December 17-18 1973 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1965, 1973 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Executive Board (1 of 4), December 10-13, 16, 19 1979 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Executive Board (2 of 4), December 10-13, 16, 19 1979 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Executive Board (3 of 4), December 10-13, 16, 19 1979 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Executive Board (4 of 4), December 10-13, 16, 19 1979 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1979 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Executive Board, April 30-May 1 1980 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Executive Board, October 22-23 1980 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1980 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Executive Board, April 8-9 1981 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Executive Board - Motions, July 24 1981 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Executive Board, September 23-25 1981 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Executive Board, March 10-11 1982 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Executive Board, September 29-30 1982 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1982 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Executive Board, April 20-21 1983 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Executive Board - Supplemental, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Western States Regional Council #3, 1964-1985; Subseries B (Box-folder 6/1-6/10)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1964 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1976 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1977 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1978 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1979 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1980 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1981 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1984 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Western States Regional Council #3, 1985 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, 1962-1980; Subseries C (Box-folder 6/11-6/28)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, May 7-8 1962 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, October 20-21 1962 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, February 7-8 1963 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, May 7-8 1963 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, November 10 1964 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, November 6 1969 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, August 16 1973 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, January 24 1974 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, May 16 1974 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, March 13 1975 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, October 30 1975 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, June 3 1976 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, August 17-18 1976 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, November 9 1976 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, November 9 1978 (Box-folder 6/25)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, June 12 1980 (Box-folder 6/26)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, August 12-13 1980 (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, November 6-1980 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Western Canadian Regional Council #1, 1965-1985; Subseries D (Box-folder 6/29-6/39)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1 - Supplements only, 1983 (Box-folder 6/29)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1980 (Box-folder 6/30)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1979 (Box-folder 6/31)
      - Report to the Officers of the 28th Annual Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 6/32)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1970 (Box-folder 6/33)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1982 (Box-folder 6/34)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1978 (Box-folder 6/35)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1976 (Box-folder 6/36)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1985 (Box-folder 6/37)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1984 (Box-folder 6/38)
      - Canadian Regional Council #1, 1976 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Southern States Regional Council #5, 1963, 1970-1971, 1975, 1978; Subseries E (Box-folder 6/40)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS-Reports of Regional Councils, 1963-1965; SERIES III (Box-folder 5/26)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD MOTIONS, 1938-1987; SERIES IV (Box-folder 7/1-7/18)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 30-May 1 1980 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Executive Board Motions, October 22-23 1980 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 8-9 1981 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Executive Board Motions, September 23-25 1981 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Executive Board Motions, March 10-11, 17, 19 1982 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Executive Board Motions, September 29-30 1982 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 20-22 1983 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Executive Board Motions, September 28-29 1983 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Executive Board Motions, March 14-16 1984 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Executive Board Motions, September 6-7 1984 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 16-17 1985 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Executive Board Motions, October 22-24 1985 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 16-17 1986 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Executive Board Motions, January 20-21 1987 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Executive Board Motions, April 22 1987 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Executive Board Motions, 1938-1961 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Executive Board Motions, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Executive Board Motions, 1938-1958 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - CONVENTION PROCEEDINGS, 1936-1987; SERIES V (Box-folder 8-10)
    - International Conventions, 1936-1987; Subseries A (Box-folder 8/1-8/11)
      - Proceedings of the First General Convention, 1936 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - First and Second Constitutional Conventions, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Third and Fourth Constitutional Conventions, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1941 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Fifth Annual Convention, 1957 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Sixth Constitutional Convention, 1942 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1943 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Eighth Constitutional Convention, 1944 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Ninth Annual Convention, 1945 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Twentieth Constitutional Convention (Volume II), 1957 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Thirty-Fourth Constitutional Convention, 1987 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Western Canadian Regional Council #1, 1945-1982; Subseries B (Box-folder 8/12-8/15, 10/23, 10/37)
      - Twentieth Annual Convention, 1957 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Twenty-fifth and Twenty-sixth Annual Convention, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Twenty-eighth and Forty-second Annual Convention, 1965, 1979 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Forty-fifth Annual Convention, 1982 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Eighth Annual Convention, 1945 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Excerpt from the Thirty-seventh Annual Convention, 1974 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - Western States Regional Council #3, 1965-1986; Subseries C (Box-folder 9/1-9/10)
      - 6th, 8th, 11th, and 12th Annual Convention, 1965, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Seventeenth Constitutional Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Nineteenth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1978 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Twentieth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1979 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Twenty-first Annual Constitutional Convention, 1980 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Twenty-second Annual Constitutional Convention, 1981 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Twenty-third Annual Constitutional Convention, 1982 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Twenty-fourth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1983 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Twenty-sixth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1985 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Twenty-seventh Annual Constitutional Convention, 1986 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Midwestern States Regional Council #4, 1964-1984; Subseries D (Box-folder 9/11-9/20)
      - Constitutional Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Seventh Biennial Convention, 1980 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Biennial Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Eighth Biennial Convention, 1984 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Annual Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Annual Convention, 1964 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Biennial Convention, 1974 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Wage Policy Conference, 1962 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Wage Policy Conference, 1963 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Wage Policy Conference, 1964 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Plywood, Box Shook and Door Council, District #9, 1956-1958; Subseries E (Box-folder 9/21-9/22)
      - Thirteenth Annual Convention, 1958 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Eleventh Annual Convention, 1956 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Southern States Regional Council, Region #5, 1963-1982; Subseries F (Box-folder 10/1-10/6)
      - Tenth Constitutional Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1964 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Fourth Constitutional Convention, 1963 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Seventh Annual Constitutional Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1982 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Thirteenth Annual Convention, 1980 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Eastern Canadian Region #2, 1959-1976; Subseries G (Box-folder 10/7-10/11, 10/24)
      - Fifth Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Tenth Annual Convention, 1966 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Fifteenth Constitutional Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Quinzieme Congres Statutaire (French Copy of the Fifteenth Constitutional Convention), 1976 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Third Annual Convention, 1959 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Ninth Annual Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Inland Empire District Council #10, 1948-1956; Subseries H (Box-folder 10/12-10/13)
      - Seventh Annual Convention, 1948 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Fifteenth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1956 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Klamath Basin District Council #6, 1940-1949; Subseries I (Box-folder 10/14-10/20)
      - Sixth Semi-Annual Convention, 1947 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Council Convention, 1940 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Eighth Annual Nominating Convention, 1949 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Sixth Annual Nominating Convention, 1947 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Seventh Annual Nominating Convention, 1948 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Ninth Semi-Annual Convention, 1949 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Assorted Local and National Meetings, 1937-1980; Subseries J (Box-folder 10/17, 10/21-10/22, 10/25-10/26, 10/28-10/30)
      - Annual Meeting of Local 1-207, 1980 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Officers' Joint Report to the Twelfth Annual Convention, Northern Washington District Council, 1948 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Officers' Joint Report to the Thirteenth Annual Convention, Northern Washington District Council, 1949 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Wage and Contract Conference, Region V, 1961 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - Federation of Woodworkers, 1937 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Tenth Annual Delegated Meeting of Local 1-417, 1968 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Local 1-423 25th Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - Disposition of matters referred to the Executive Council by the Sixth Constitutional Convention of the Canadian Labour Congress, 1966 (Box-folder 10/30)
- International Woodworkers of America records, 1936-1942; 4000-002; 0.18 cubic feet (1 box) 1 bound volume
  Minutes of reports of meetings, 1936-1937, 1940-1942.